[{"answer": "Well, if it's any consolation, I did get her number", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Aw, I doubt you strained it. Maybe you pulled it", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " I'm not engaged. my friend gives my friend a look. my friend enters. He's carrying a small goldfish bowl, a pad and a pencil tied to the bowl by string", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Got what", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Ah, I got it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Got the answer, my friend. Refrigerator problem, is solved", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Got the answer, my friend. Refrigerator problem, is solved", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Oh, I will. But now, I'm accountable. Alright, I take what I want. my friend takes a cupcake from a box on the counter", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You know, my friend, just because your life is destroyed, don't Destroy someone else's", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "How about 'my friend'", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You cannot buy half a can of soda", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " Oh, ah.  Stupid my friend. my friend is looking in a shop window, then she spots my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Huh? my friend comes over to my friend. All my friend can see of her is her head and neck", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " I'm fine", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " Okay, oh, it was good to, good to see you. my friend comes along the street, riding the Schwinn Stingray and ringing the bell. He attracts comments from folk on the street", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " What happened to Soda?! I thought we all agreed on Soda", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You don't care for Soda?", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Just keep breathing, okay", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Okay", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well, if it's any consolation, I did get her number", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Aw, I doubt you strained it. Maybe you pulled it", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " I'm not engaged. my friend gives my friend a look. my friend enters. He's carrying a small goldfish bowl, a pad and a pencil tied to the bowl by string", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Got what", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Ah, I got it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " Got the answer, my friend. Refrigerator problem, is solved", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " Got the answer, my friend. Refrigerator problem, is solved", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Oh, I will. But now, I'm accountable. Alright, I take what I want. my friend takes a cupcake from a box on the counter", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "You know, my friend, just because your life is destroyed, don't Destroy someone else's", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "How about 'my friend'", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You cannot buy half a can of soda", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " Oh, ah.  Stupid my friend. my friend is looking in a shop window, then she spots my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Huh? my friend comes over to my friend. All my friend can see of her is her head and neck", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " I'm fine", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " Okay, oh, it was good to, good to see you. my friend comes along the street, riding the Schwinn Stingray and ringing the bell. He attracts comments from folk on the street", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " What happened to Soda?! I thought we all agreed on Soda", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "You don't care for Soda?", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Just keep breathing, okay", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Okay", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Well, if it's any consolation, I did get her number", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Aw, I doubt you strained it. Maybe you pulled it", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " I'm not engaged. my friend gives my friend a look. my friend enters. He's carrying a small goldfish bowl, a pad and a pencil tied to the bowl by string", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Got what", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Ah, I got it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": " Got the answer, my friend. Refrigerator problem, is solved", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": " Got the answer, my friend. Refrigerator problem, is solved", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Oh, I will. But now, I'm accountable. Alright, I take what I want. my friend takes a cupcake from a box on the counter", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "You know, my friend, just because your life is destroyed, don't Destroy someone else's", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "How about 'my friend'", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "You cannot buy half a can of soda", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": " Oh, ah.  Stupid my friend. my friend is looking in a shop window, then she spots my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Huh? my friend comes over to my friend. All my friend can see of her is her head and neck", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": " I'm fine", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": " Okay, oh, it was good to, good to see you. my friend comes along the street, riding the Schwinn Stingray and ringing the bell. He attracts comments from folk on the street", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": " What happened to Soda?! I thought we all agreed on Soda", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "You don't care for Soda?", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Just keep breathing, okay", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Okay", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Well, if it's any consolation, I did get her number", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Aw, I doubt you strained it. Maybe you pulled it", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": " I'm not engaged. my friend gives my friend a look. my friend enters. He's carrying a small goldfish bowl, a pad and a pencil tied to the bowl by string", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Got what", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "Ah, I got it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": " Got the answer, my friend. Refrigerator problem, is solved", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": " Got the answer, my friend. Refrigerator problem, is solved", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Oh, I will. But now, I'm accountable. Alright, I take what I want. my friend takes a cupcake from a box on the counter", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "You know, my friend, just because your life is destroyed, don't Destroy someone else's", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "How about 'my friend'", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "You cannot buy half a can of soda", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": " Oh, ah.  Stupid my friend. my friend is looking in a shop window, then she spots my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "Huh? my friend comes over to my friend. All my friend can see of her is her head and neck", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": " I'm fine", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": " Okay, oh, it was good to, good to see you. my friend comes along the street, riding the Schwinn Stingray and ringing the bell. He attracts comments from folk on the street", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": " What happened to Soda?! I thought we all agreed on Soda", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "You don't care for Soda?", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "Just keep breathing, okay", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Seven.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "Okay", "qsentId": 80}]